Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Indiana Division of Publicity, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana Secretary of State, 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana State Scholarships, 1940-1943; (3 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana Sesquicentennial, 1949-1962; (5 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana State Board of Revenue, 1949-1950 (Box 295)
  - Indiana State Board of Review, 1950-1952; (2 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana State Officials, 1949-1950 (Box 295)
  - Indiana School Facilities Study, 1950-1952; (2 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana State School Survey Commission, 1950-1952; (2 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana State Teachers Retirement Fund, 1937-1952; (14 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana Toll Road Commission, 1954-1960; (6 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana State Treasurer, 1942-1952; (10 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana Division of Veterans Affairs, 1952-1962; (10 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana Miscellaneous, 1940-1946; (6 folders) (Box 295)
  - Indiana-Miscellaneous, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 296)
  - Indiana Academy of Social Sciences, 1938-1943; (5 folders) (Box 296)
  - Indiana Almanac and Government Guide, 1961-1962 (Box 296)
  - Indiana Alumni Magazine, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 296)
  - Indiana Artists Club, 1939-1943; (4 folders) (Box 296)
  - Indiana Association of Church Related and Independent Colleges, 1948-1950; (2 folders) (Box 296)
  - Indiana Anti-Syphilis Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 296)
  - Indiana Bankers Association Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 296)
  - Indiana Bankers Association, 1938-1951; (14 folders) (Box 297)
  - Indiana Bankers Association, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 298)
  - Indiana Banking Conference, 1938-1942; (7 folders) (Box 298)
  - Indiana Bell Telephone Company, 1937-1955; (23 folders) (Box 298)
  - Indiana Bell Telephone Company, 1954-1962; (16 folders) (Box 299)
  - Indiana Business Review, 1939-1943; (2 folders) (Box 299)
  - Indiana Central College, 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 299)
  - Indiana Colleges, 1944-1945 (Box 299)
  - Indiana Committee for Victory (Box 299)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 299)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 299)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 299)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 299)
  - Indiana Conference of Institutions of Higher Education, 1944-1950; (7 folders) (Box 299)
  - Indiana Conference of Higher Education, 1950-1961; (21 folders) (Box 300)
  - Indiana Conference of Higher Education, 1961-1962 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Council on Education, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 301)
  - Indiana Daily Student, 1937-1959; (46 folders) (Box 301)
  - Indiana Farmers Guide, 1938-1939 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Federation of Art Clubs, 1938-1939 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Federation of Clubs, 1937-1950; (15 folders) (Box 301)
  - Indiana Federation of Music Clubs, 1942-1949; (6 folders) (Box 301)
  - Indiana Federation of Women's Clubs, 1950-1952; (2 folders) (Box 301)
  - Indiana Flying Club, 1938-1939 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Gas and Water Company, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Historical Bureau, 1944-1945 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Inspection Bureau, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 301)
  - Indiana Institute, 1945-1946 (Box 302)
  - Indiana Institute in Library Adult Education, 1958-1959 (Box 302)
  - Indiana Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1939-1946; (2 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Junior Historical Society, 1939-1940 (Box 302)
  - Indiana Law Journal, 1948-1952; (5 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana League of Women Voters, 1939-1949; (8 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Legislative Bureau, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Library Association, 1938-1939 (Box 302)
  - Indiana Magazine of History, 1941-1962; (22 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Music Appreciation, 1939-1940 (Box 302)
  - Indian Names of Indiana Streams and Lakes, 1946-1947 (Box 302)
  - Indianapolis Symphony Buffet, 1946-1947 (Box 302)
  - Wells, H.B -Indianapolis Tea, January 26, 1947 (Box 302)
  - Indiana National Bank, 1937-1961; (24 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Purdue Foundation at Fort Wayne, 1957-1960; (3 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Purdue University, 1959-1960 (Box 302)
  - Indiana Purdue Foundation, 1960-1962; (3 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana Schoolmen's Club, 1937-1953; (16 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana School of Religion, 1952-1962; (12 folders) (Box 302)
  - Indiana School Planning Laboratory Fund, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 302)
  - Indiana School Laboratory Fund, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 303)
  - Indiana Society of Chicago, 1938-1962; (23 folders) (Box 303)
  - Indiana Society for Mental Hygiene, 1939-1942 (Box 303)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 303)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 303)
  - Indiana State Board of Health, 1944-1945 (Box 303)
  - Indiana State Chamber of Commerce, 1941-1954; (14 folders) (Box 303)
  - Indiana State Chamber of Commerce, 1954-1962; (10 folders) (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Conference on Problems of Post-War Higher Education, 1943-1944 (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Employees Association (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Federation of Labor, 1939-1944; (3 folders) (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Planning Conference, 1938-1939 (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Schools, 1944-1948; (2 folders) (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Teachers College, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 304)
  - Indiana State Teachers College, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1943-1962; (20 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Student Association, 1938-1943; (4 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Tax Study Commission, 1939 (Box 305)
  - Indiana Technical College, 1946-1957; (8 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Trust Company, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana White House Conference on Education, 1955 (Box 305)
  - Indiana Memorial Union, 1937-1962; (15 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Union and Indiana Union Food Department, 1939-1948; (6 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Student Union and Food Service Building, 1956-1961; (5 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Union, 1937-1942; (9 folders) (Box 305)
  - Indiana Union, 1942-1952; (29 folders) (Box 306)
  - Indiana Union, 1949-1960; (38 folders) (Box 307)
  - Indiana Union, 1960-1962; (11 folders) (Box 308)
  - Indiana University-Alumni Club of Indianapolis, 1938-1955; (17 folders) (Box 308)
  - Indiana University Calendars, 1961-1962 (Box 308)
  - Indiana University Foundation, 1937-1953; (31 folders) (Box 308)
  - Indiana University Foundation, 1952-1956; (23 folders) (Box 309)
  - Indiana University Foundation, 1955-1959; (21 folders) (Box 310)
  - Indiana University Foundation, 1958-1962; (7 folders) (Box 311)
  - Indiana University Research Committee, 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 311)
  - Indiana University Foundation, 1961-1962; (4 folders) (Box 312)
  - Indiana University Men's Club (Box 312)
  - Indiana University Newsletter (Box 312)
  - Indiana University Printing Plant Reports, etc., 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 312)
  - Indiana University Research Committee, 1956-1961; (5 folders) (Box 312)
  - Indiana University Women's Club, 1938-1939 (Box 312)
  - Indiana War History Commission, 1942-1950; (15 folders) (Box 312)
  - Indiana War History Commission, 1950-1959; (8 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indiana Women's Biography Association, 1939-1940 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis, 1940-1962; (17 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Alumni Club, 1947-1948 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Art Association Herron Art Institute, 1938-1939 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Athletic Club, 1937-1962; (22 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Bar Association Building, 1944-1945 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Baseball Club (Indianapolis Indians), 1943 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Bond and Share Corporation, 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Bulletin Regarding Things that are happening, 1937-1938 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Civic Theater, 1939-1942; (3 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Commission Space, 1946-1949; (2 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Community Fund, 1945-1946 (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Concerts and Forums, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Council on World Affairs, 1956-1961; (5 folders) (Box 313)
  - Indianapolis Council on World Affairs, 1961-1962 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Dormitory, 1939-1940 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Engraving Company (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Hospital Development Association, 1952 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Houses and Rentals, 1965 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis-Miscellaneous, 1949-1950 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis News-Star and Times, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Press Club, 1937-1952; (7 folders) (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Real Estate Board, 1938-1942; (4 folders) (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Recorder, 1938 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Star, 1960-1961 (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, 1937-1952; (17 folders) (Box 314)
  - Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, 1952-1962; (10 folders) (Box 314)
  - Indonesia, 1958-1959 (Box 314)
    - ICA Contract, 1958-1962; (7 folders) (Box 314)
  - Bureau of Industrial and Labor Services, 1959-1960 (Box 314)
  - Industrial Relations, 1945-1949; (4 folders) (Box 314)
    - Research Fellowships, 1943-1944 (Box 314)
    - Survey, 1938-1939 (Box 314)
  - Institutes, 1952-1957; (5 folders) (Box 314)
  - Institutes, 1957-1962; (5 folders) (Box 315)
  - Institute for Personnel and Guidance Work, 1944-1946; (2 folders) (Box 315)
  - Institute of Training for Public Service, 1945-1946 (Box 315)
  - Institute for Sex Research, 1954-1961; (6 folders) (Box 315)
  - Institute for Training for Public Service, 1946-1947 (Box 315)
  - Institute of Adult Education, 1941-1942 (Box 315)
  - Institute of Criminal Law, 1937-1949; (9 folders) (Box 315)
  - Institute of International Education, 1937-1962; (31 folders) (Box 315)
  - Institute of Politics Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 315)
  - Institute for College Teachers of Botany (Box 315)
  - Institute of Training for Public Service, 1950-1958; (10 folders) (Box 315)
  - Institute of Training for Public Service, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 316)
  - Insurance, 1937-1946; (31 folders) (Box 316)
  - Insurance, 1946-1962; (32 folders) (Box 317)
  - Inter, 1940-1961; (16 folders) (Box 317)
  - Inter, 1961-1962 (Box 318)
  - Inter-American Affairs, 1942-1946; (4 folders) (Box 318)
  - Inter-American Conference, 1942-1943 (Box 318)
  - Inter-American Institute, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 318)
  - Intercollegiate-Athletic Department, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 318)
    - Conference, 1937-1960; (27 folders) (Box 318)
  - Intercollegiate Conference, 1960-1962; (21 folders) (Box 319)
  - Inter Institutional Study, (2 folders) (Box 319)
  - International Affairs, 1960-1961 (Box 319)
  - International Association of Chiefs of Police, 1961-1962 (Box 319)
  - International Association of Chiefs of Police of Universities, 1958 (Box 319)
  - International Benjamin Franklin Society, 1961-1962 (Box 319)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 319)
  - International Educational Services, 1957-1958 (Box 319)
  - Iraq, Institute of Public Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 319)
  - International Journal of America, 1943-1944 (Box 319)
  - International Journal of American Linguistics, 1944-1946; (2 folders) (Box 319)
  - International Office of Education, 1944-1945 (Box 319)
  - International Organization, 1945-1947; (2 folders) (Box 319)
  - International Relations, 1938-1944; (4 folders) (Box 319)
  - Interpreting the University of the State, 1948-1949 (Box 319)
  - Inter-University, 1946-1962; (6 folders) (Box 319)
  - Intramural News Bulletin, 1938-1939 (Box 319)
  - Inventory, 1950-1952; (3 folders) (Box 319)
  - Investigations (Box 319)
  - Investments, 1956-1961; (3 folders) (Box 320)
    - Committee, 1938-1951; (24 folders) (Box 320)
  - Investment Committee, 1950-1955; (12 folders) (Box 321)
  - Inventory of Securities by type of securities, 1955; (3 folders) (Box 321)
  - Investment Committee, 1955-1956; (2 folders) (Box 321)
  - Securities by Fund, 1956 (Box 321)
  - Investment-Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 321)
    - Record, 1957; (2 folders) (Box 321)
    - Committee, 1957-1961; (5 folders) (Box 321)
  - Investment-Committee, 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 322)
    - Research Bureau, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 322)
  - Investments, 1958; (2 folders) (Box 322)
    - School for American Life Insurance Convention, 1939-1940 (Box 322)
  - Invitations to be Extended, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 322)
  - Iowa State College, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 322)
  - Iowa State Teachers College, 1937-1949; (11 folders) (Box 322)
  - Iowa State University, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 322)
  - Ir, 1937-1960; (23 folders) (Box 322)
  - Ir, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 323)
  - Is, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 323)
  - Isabell, Joseph W., 1939-1940 (Box 323)
  - Itinerant Teacher Trainer for Distributive Occupations, 1937-1938 (Box 323)
  - Itinerant Police Training, 1937-1938 (Box 323)
  - Itinerant Teacher Trainer for Home Economics, 1937-1938 (Box 323)
  - Itinerant Teacher Training, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 323)
  - Ittner, Dr. Robert T., 1938-1948; (6 folders) (Box 323)
  - Izor, Charles E., 1937-1938 (Box 323)
  - J, 1937-1959; (22 folders) (Box 323)
  - J, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 324)
  - Jack, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 324)
  - Jackson, 1947-1948 (Box 324)
  - Jackson, Elmer, 1947-1948 (Box 324)
  - Jackson, Lida B. (Box 324)
  - Jackson, Margaret Weymouth Saturday Evening Stories, 1939-1940 (Box 324)
  - Jackson, Paul, 1938-1946 (Box 324)
  - Jackson, Samuel, 1944-1945 (Box 324)
  - Jaco, 1937-1957; (21 folders) (Box 324)
  - Jahn Educational Foundation Lecture (Box 324)
  - Jaco, 1959-1962; (4 folders) (Box 324)
  - Jacobson Brothers, 1937-1938 (Box 324)
  - Jae, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 324)
  - Jam, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 324)
  - James, Edmund J., 1954-1955 (Box 324)
  - James, Edward D. (Box 324)
    - 1938-1954 (Box 324)
    - 1954-1962 (Box 324)
  - Thelma James, 1943 (Box 324)
  - Jan, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 324)
  - Janitorial Services, 1939-1940 (Box 324)
  - Janitors' Questionnaire, 1938-1939 (Box 324)
  - Japanese-Orientation Program, 1950 (Box 324)
  - Japanese Students (Box 324)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 324)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 324)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 324)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 324)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 324)
  - Jay, John and Hilda (Lease), 1939-1957 (Box 324)
  - Je, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 324)
  - Je, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 325)
  - Jellema, Prof. W.H. (Box 325)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 325)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 325)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 325)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 325)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 325)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 325)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 325)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 325)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 325)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 325)
  - Jen, 1953-1954 (Box 325)
  - Jenner, William E., 1949-1953; (4 folders) (Box 325)
  - Jens, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 325)
  - Jen, 1948-1949 (Box 325)
  - Jens, 1943-1954; (10 folders) (Box 325)
  - Jen, 1954-1955 (Box 325)
  - Jens, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 325)
  - Jessup, Dr. Walter A., 1940-1941 (Box 325)
  - Jews or Jewish (general), 1938-1959 (Box 325)
    Note: Includes records from or about Jewish students and correspondence with or about Jewish organizations or issues.
    - 1939-1942 (Box 325)
    - 1943-1945 (Box 325)
    - 1946-1959 (Box 325)
  - Jo, 1937-1942; (6 folders) (Box 325)
  - Jo, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 326)
  - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1942-1950; (8 folders) (Box 326)
  - Johns, 1937-1938 (Box 326)
  - Johns, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 327)
  - Johnson, 1942-1962; (22 folders) (Box 327)
  - Johnson, Harvey L., 1951-1956 (Box 327)
    (Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese)
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1956-1958; (2 folders) (Box 327)
  - Johnst, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 327)
  - Joint Committee on Voluntary Support, 1961-1962 (Box 328)
  - Joint Advisory Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 328)
  - Jol, 1941-1961; (14 folders) (Box 328)
  - Jon, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 328)
  - Jones, Howard P., 1942-1943 (Box 328)
  - Jones, 1942-1955; (21 folders) (Box 328)
  - Jones, Howard P., 1938-1942; (5 folders) (Box 328)
  - Jor, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 328)
  - Jor, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 329)
  - Jordan Field, 1946-1948 (Box 329)
  - Jordan, Harold W., 1939-1962; (11 folders) (Box 329)
  - Jordan Hall (Box 329)
    - General (Box 329)
      - 1952-1955 (Box 329)
      - January - April 1956 (Box 329)
      - May 1956 (Box 329)
      - June 1956 (Box 329)
      - July 1956-1957 (Box 329)
    - Lieber Room, 1956 (Box 329)
  - Jordan River Revue, 1937-1938 (Box 329)
  - Jos, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 329)
  - Journalism Applications, 1938-1940 (Box 329)
  - Journalism Department, 1937-1938; (2 folders) (Box 329)
  - Journalism Conference at I.U., 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 329)
  - Ju, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 329)
  - Judd, Dr. Charles H., 1939-1940 (Box 329)
  - Judd, Hon. Lawrence M., 1939-1940 (Box 329)
  - Jung, Christian W., 1953-1954 (Box 329)
  - Junior-Chamber of Commerce Award Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 329)
    - College Bill in Legislation, 1938-1939 (Box 329)
    - Divison, 1937-1942; (11 folders) (Box 329)
  - Junior Division, 1942-1962; (17 folders) (Box 330)
  - Junior Year Abroad (Box 330)
  - Junior Year in Peru, 1961-1962 (Box 330)
  - K, 1937-1956; (20 folders) (Box 330)
  - K, 1956-1962; (6 folders) (Box 331)
  - Kal, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 331)
  - Kaler Candy and Tobacco Company, 1944-1945 (Box 331)
  - Kan, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 331)
  - Kansas University, 1954-1955 (Box 331)
  - Kansas City Invitation to President Wells, 1939-1940 (Box 331)
  - Kansas State Agricultural College, 1937-1949; (9 folders) (Box 331)
  - Kansas State Teachers Association, 1938-1939 (Box 331)
  - Kansas State Teachers College, 1939-1942; (6 folders) (Box 331)
  - University of Kansas, 1937-1938 (Box 331)
  - Kansas State Teachers College, 1942-1943 (Box 331)
  - University of Kansas, 1938-1961; (22 folders) (Box 331)
  - Kantor, J.R., 1942-1946 (Box 331)
  - Kap, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 331)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi
    - 1940-1953 (Box 331)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 331)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 331)
    - 1957-1961 (Box 331)
  - Kar, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 331)
  - Karpinski, Dr. Robert Whitcomb, 1938-1939 (Box 331)
  - Kas, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 332)
  - Kau, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 332)
  - Ke, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 332)
  - Kee, 1937-1955; (7 folders) (Box 333)
  - Keedy, John C. (Box 333)
  - Kei, 1949-1950 (Box 333)
  - Kel, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 333)
  - Keller, O.E.M., 1945-1949; (4 folders) (Box 333)
  - Keller Crescent Co., 1942-1944; (2 folders) (Box 333)
  - Kellogg, Winthrop N., 1937-1950; (6 folders) (Box 333)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1953-1954 (Box 333)
  - Kemp, Gretchen, 1948-1962 (Box 333)
  - Ken, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 333)
  - Ken, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 334)
  - Kennedy's Cabinet Members, 1960-1961 (Box 334)
  - Kentucky Bankers Conference, 1939-1940 (Box 334)
  - University of Kentucky, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 334)
  - Kentucky Western State Normal School, 1937-1942; (4 folders) (Box 334)
  - Kenworthy, Edwin W., 1939-1940 (Box 334)
  - Ker, 1937-1959; (21 folders) (Box 334)
  - Ker, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kes, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 335)
  - Key, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 335)
  - Ki, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kil, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kilgore Bill, 1942-1943 (Box 335)
  - Kim, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kimberling, Nancy Lou, 1949 (Box 335)
  - Kime, Dr. Edwin, 1940-1953; (13 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kime, Posey, 1946-1947 (Box 335)
  - Kimble, George H.T., 1956-1962; (6 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kimmel, George C., 1939-1940 (Box 335)
  - Kin, 1937-1942; (3 folders) (Box 335)
  - Kin, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 336)
  - King, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 336)
  - King, L.M., 1937-1938 (Box 336)
  - Kingan and Company, 1941-1942 (Box 336)
  - Kinge, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 336)
  - Kingsbury, Charles L., 1943-1951 (Box 336)
  - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1937-1958 (Box 336)
    - 1937-1947 (Box 336)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 336)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 336)
      Includes "Kinsey's 'Sexual Behavior in the Human Male': Some Comments and Criticism," by Lewis M. Terman, Psychological Bulletin, Vol. 45, No. 5, September, 1948
    - 1949-1950 (Box 336)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 336)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 336)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 336)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 336)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 336)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 336)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 336)
  - Kir, 1937-1950; (13 folders) (Box 336)
  - Kir, 1950-1962; (12 folders) (Box 337)
  - Kirby, Mrs. Lottie M., 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 337)
  - Kirk, Dorothea, 1941-1942 (Box 337)
  - Kirkwood Observatory Anniversary, 1947-1948 (Box 337)
  - Kissinger, Henry (Box 337)
  - Kittisak Jirngsa-ard Memorial Fund, 1959-1960 (Box 337)
  - Kl, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 337)
  - Kli, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 337)
  - Kn, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 337)
  - Kn, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 338)
  - Kneubuh, Emily, 1938-1939 (Box 338)
  - Knight House, 1939-1940 (Box 338)
  - Kno, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 338)
  - Ko, 1937-1958; (21 folders) (Box 338)
  - Ko, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 339)
  - Koe, 1949-1950 (Box 339)
  - Koh, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 339)
  - Kohlmeier, Prof. A.L., 1937-1953; (16 folders) (Box 339)
  - Konopinske, Emil, 1938-1962 (Box 339)
  - Kom, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 339)
  - Koo, 1949-1950 (Box 339)
  - Koon, Archie M., 1951 (Box 339)
  - Kor, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 339)
  - Korean Contract (Nursing Education), 1961-1962 (Box 339)
  - Kos, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 339)
  - Kr, 1937-1960; (22 folders) (Box 339)
  - Kr, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 340)
  - Krauss, Paul III, 1940-1943; (3 folders) (Box 340)
  - Kre, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 340)
  - Kr, 1955-1956 (Box 340)
  - Kre, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 340)
  - Kress Galleries, 1939-1955 (Box 340)
  - Kri, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 340)
  - Kro, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 340)
  - Kroc, Dr. Robert L., 1937-1938 (Box 340)
  - Kroger Scholarships, 1939-1940 (Box 340)
  - Kronenberger, Albrecht M., 1950-1958 (Box 340)
  - Kru, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 340)
  - Ku, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 340)
  - Kul, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 340)
  - Ku, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 341)
  - Kuhn, Virginia Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 341)
  - Kunkel, William A., Jr., 1937-1949; (12 folders) (Box 341)
  - L, 1937-1957; (20 folders) (Box 341)
  - L, 1957-1962; (5 folders) (Box 342)
  - Labor and Personnel Relations Meeting, 1944-1945 (Box 342)
  - Labor Education, 1945-1959; (5 folders) (Box 342)
  - Laboratory Schools, 1939-1940 (Box 342)
  - Laboratory Technicians, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 342)
  - Laf, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 342)
  - Lafayette Bicentennial, 1957-1958 (Box 342)
  - Lafayette Fellowship Foundation, Inc., 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 342)
  - Lak, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 342)
  - Lake Central Airlines, 1954-1955 (Box 342)
  - Lake County Day Program, 1937-1938 (Box 342)
  - Lam, 1937-1955; (11 folders) (Box 342)
  - Lan, 1937-1950; (13 folders) (Box 342)
  - Lan, 1950-1962; (12 folders) (Box 343)
  - Land-Grant Colleges Convention in K.C., 1961 (Box 343)
  - Landis, Col. John F., 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 343)
  - Landon, Hugh McK., 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 343)
  - Landscape Work, 1938-1939 (Box 343)
  - Langer, Lawrence M., 1941-1943 (Box 343)
  - Archives of the Languages of the World, 1953-1954 (Box 343)
  - Language, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 343)
    - Laboratory, 1953-1954 (Box 343)
    - Conference, 1960 (Box 343)
    - Teaching, 1945-1946 (Box 343)
    - Training (Box 343)
  - General Modern, 1938-1940 (Box 343)
  - Lar, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 344)
  - Larson, L.C., 1942-1952; (10 folders) (Box 344)
  - Las, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 344)
  - Laski, Harold J., 1939-1940 (Box 344)
  - Last Lecture Series (Box 344)
  - Latin, 1948-1951 (Box 344)